# 14631 MELCO AVENUE PARKER, CO 80134 PHONE 303 909 1532 • E-MAIL | GREGORYSTRONG@GMAIL.COM

# JON GREGORY

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Full stack developer, passionate about technology and continuous improvement is seeking a software development role which will assist in the corporate strategies to produce positive financial returns. Over the past 13 years I have become well versed in operations, engineering, and business development of the oil and gas industry. I am now taking the skill sets I have acquired over my career and integrating them with software engineering. I am confident that I would make a positive contribution and would appreciate your consideration of my skills in this application.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## 2/19 - 4/20 Citadel Casing Solutions

- Generated new and grew existing relationships for accounts in the Rockies, West Coast, and Canada.
- Generated revenue over plan of 300% during Q1 2020.
- Identified customer needs and provided engineered solutions while maintaining focus on maximizing profitability.

#### 4/18 - 2/19 Distribution NOW

• Generated new accounts for a startup industrial pump business in Colorado.

# 11/2007 - 8/2017 Halliburton Energy Services

## Engineer / Account Leader / Business Development Manager

- Responsible for understanding revenue/cost structures and pricing for all
  product service lines to multiple customers in the Rockies and western United
  States.
- Managed 25+ account reps covering multiple service lines.
- Responsible for roughly \$650,000,000.00 in yearly revenue.
- Worked with customer engineering teams to produce value add, engineered solutions for common to complex problems.
- Presented performance reviews to customers.
- Established communication and built lasting relationships with customers from the C-suite to the engineering level.
- Responsible for creation of and maintaining T&Cs for all customer service contracts.
- Subject matter expert in oilfield cement engineering and operations.

#### 6/2001 - 8/2007 Smart Solutions LLC.

- Started a private technical consulting company.
- Consulted on a variety of solutions to 15+ clients.
- SQL, Java, JS, HTML, CSS,

## 11/2000 - 11/2001 Wellogix, Inc.

 Developed prototype applications for a startup petroleum exploration and drilling software company. Java, SQL, Oracle, JS, HTML, CSS, C++

#### 5/1999 - 11/2000 International Business Machines

 Worked on multiple teams for several high visibility projects. (www.wiredscholar.com, www.helzberg.com, Sprint.com) Java, SQL, Oracle, JS, HTML, CSS, C++

#### **EDUCATION**

#### 2021 - University of Denver - Full stack software boot camp

• HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, React, Node.js, MySql, MongoDB, Bootstrap,

# 2012 - 2015 Texas A&M University - Mays Business School - Center for Executive Development

- Financial acumen
- Business Leadership Development I & II

#### 1994 - 1999 Colorado State University

Ft. Collins, CO

• Bachelor Degree, Economics

#### AWARDS AND MEMBERSHIPS

Github: <a href="https://github.com/jongregory75">https://github.com/jongregory75</a>

Portfolio: https://jongregory75.github.io/Portfolio/

# 2012 MVP - Halliburton Energy Services

• Award given by peers for top of class in Frontline Supervisor Training

# 2012 MVP - Halliburton Energy Services.

• Award for providing exceptional solutions to customers.

#### 2000 Client Team Award - IBM

Award for outstanding team contribution